Homie and so Amanda Seales was recently
on live stream going in on Charlamagne
tha God, all right? She was going in on
that boy calling him a snake. Now this
is crazy to me because out of so many
different fallouts that she's had in
Hollywood, just in the entertainment
industry, the one person that I've seen
that's been there for her or given her
platforms to to her side has always been
Charlamagne tha God. So this is
interesting, but here what she got to
say. Would I do a podcast with
Charlamagne?
Why did Why did Why Why would I do a
podcast with Charlamagne? We had great
chemistry until I realized that he was a
ridiculous person and he was a snake. So
then we don't have great chemistry
anymore. He's also not an intellectual.
Like he's read books, he's not a dummy,
but he's not an intellectual and he's
not
he don't got no backbone.
He sits here, he regurgitates the same
crap, and the people that he does
challenge, like remember when he
challenged Kamala Harris? Remember when
she was on his show and he was like, "So
who's actually in charge of the
Democrats? You know, uh Joe Biden or Joe
Manchin?" And she black woman'd him and
started saying like, "No, absolutely
not.
She didn't need He didn't even come back
because he didn't have no He didn't have
no way to come back at her cuz he didn't
know anything further than what he said.
And then they have people on the show
and
they allow them to just talk they sh and
to talk they [ __ ] And they don't have
the actual knowledge and the actual
intellectualism
and or the actual backbone to be able to
check them and reveal the nonsense that
they're spewing. And whether that's
Larry Elder or that other broad
or
um the guy from the ADL
etc.
Like sit to rappers.
Yes, Andrew Schulz can say whatever.
And then he defends him. So, you know
go for it, playboy, but that's not my
peoples no more.
What is that? What's your point? Back in
the day is not today.
And it's funny how people show you love
when you're beneath them.
And then once you start finding your
footing, it's funny how they don't.
And people know who they can control.
You know what I'm saying? Like people
know who they can control, people know
who they can't control a lot of times.
And so I think there's just been many
times where I was confused as to why
people weren't looking out for me
only to realize like, "Oh, it's because
they can't control me and they know
that."
Because they want to work with people
who they will always have a thumb on.
Like I had a show called
um The Big Seales, which was basically
like a mockumentary show. It turned The
name also It developed into Amanda
Seales is Difficult. And it was going to
be like a mockumentary
of me working in Hollywood. And
um
Charlamagne was going to executive
produce it. And so we were pitching it
to VH1 and then his
manager and his business manager claimed
that he created it.
And then it was his idea.
And my agent was like
no, that's that's not how No. I No.
And they were standing on that. Like,
"Well, we're not going to move forward
unless he gets creator credit because he
created it." He did not create it.
And then I had to call him
and be like, "I need you to call your
people
and get them in line."
And I don't care.
But
why would they even feel like they could
do that?
Why would they even have that idea in
their mind?
Why had that not been clarified from
jump? All right, now I don't know their
business, I don't know their business as
far as what they got going on and what
could have happened behind the scenes,
but I'mma tell you right now just just
know her track record. It's like she
falls out with everybody. So the only
people that's going to like, you know,
really believe you or be on your side in
this is folks who just don't like
Charlamagne. You know how this [ __ ] go
with internet the internet. When you
don't like someone and something comes
across your newsfeed about them, if it's
negative then you're more inclined to
believe that it was the truth. Seeing
her interactions and how she processes
things, I'm more inclined to believe
that something was misinterpreted and
taken out of context and she ran with
her narrative and that's the only
narrative that matters. Now I may be
100% wrong and I have no problem with
being wrong, but based on her digital
footprint, everybody's got problems with
her. Why you? Out of everyone, why you?
Now this comment session is an example
of what I'm referring to in regards to
her digital footprint. It says, "I just
think she showed Charlamagne what
everybody else saw. At first he was
super protective of her and cool with
her." This person says, "Who would want
to do work with this woman ever? She's
always complaining about something. Um
someone is always the problem, it's
never her. It's always everybody else to
say her. It was her customers last week,
Charlamagne this week. Just stop posting
her, she is the problem. It screams
bitterness, no accountability. Wait, she
just realized that Charlamagne is a
snake? Well, they said Charlamagne gay.
Um this lady is the most bitter person
around, she lives in this victim
mentality and it is unfortunate, zero
accountability, everything is other
people harming her. Um you can tell she
thinks she's the smartest person in
every room she walks in. And more on
more people saying [ __ ] This also This
one person is on her side saying, "He
also gets his talking points from Angela
Rye with her elite problematic behind."
Now a couple weeks ago she had this to
say about Charlamagne and Angela Rye.
Democrats and Republicans are on one
team. Anybody who doesn't thinks that
Anybody who tells you otherwise you
should not be listening to. That goes
for Joy Reid, Angela Rye, Charlamagne,
all of them. Anybody who is talking
about Democrats as if they are some
as if they are redeemable.
As if they are redeemable.
Want to keep everybody who listens to me
um just alert and oriented that, you
know, this is not a Republican-Democrat
thing. This is not a Republicans versus
the Democrat thing. You know, people
interview a politician and then swear
that the politician told them the truth.
It's actually a a very bizarre concept
to me.
Um
because people
I I mean I I actually I interviewed one
politician
on Views for Amandaland
and collectively the audience said,
"Let's just not do that anymore."
In the past we've seen she had issues
with everyone on the set of Insecure.
She even had issues with Issa Rae, you
feel me? And Issa Rae, when asked about
who she wouldn't work with again in the
future Person that I would never work
with again.
I mean, anybody who was on my podcast to
tell Charlamagne about that is crazy.
waiting to shoot.
And we were chit-chatting. Everybody
together as a group was all
chit-chatting. And we started talking
about this new show, a new show had come
out, okay?
And as we started talking about the new
show that come out, Issa started reading
a
reading a review of the show out loud to
the group, okay? She's reading the show
out loud to the group. So we're all
sitting there listening and we're all
commenting and involved in the
commentary and in the conversation.
Everybody as a group is talking. And
when I say everybody I mean the cast
members. We're all chit-chatting about
it, okay?
Together, all of us together.
And she fell off from the conversation
because she was reading the rest of the
article to herself. So then she at the I
guess when she was done reading she
said, "Oh,
yeah, it ends with da da da da da da."
And I asked, "Oh, well did they mention
da da da da da da?" And she said, "Why
don't you just read it yourself?"
And that was the last day.
Because I had taken so much strangeness
and weirdness for the past five seasons.
And it was the last season.
And I just said, "You know what? I DON'T
[screaming] GOT TO TAKE THIS NO MORE.
I don't know who the [ __ ] you talking
to.
I don't know why you're even addressing
me this way. We're in a whole group of
people together.
We're all discussing this. I'm actually
showing interest. And so that was the
last day. And I have never spoken to her
again.
Because I'm always going to show you
respect unless you play me.
Which I have one time got out of my face
because I felt played.
And then
she then
tried to act like she was going to fight
me when we was on stage doing a read at
a read
>> [laughter]
>> a read about a movie and I was like,
"Stop cuz you not We not about to
fight." And then we were able to have a
civil conversation after that. I I I
listen, she got in her feelings, fine.
Bye, fine, fine. But trying to sun me,
not trying, sunning me in front of
everybody is unacceptable for a number
of reasons. One,
I am your employee.
I'm your employee. That's number one. I
don't You're sunning me for what like
I'm not It's not that I didn't anything
wrong. It's not like you're correcting
me in the work. Two, I am your peer
colleague and three I'm your elder.
Boom, boom, boom.
So that was the last day.
I'm not doing it. I'm not going to keep
putting up with this behavior. I'm not
going to keep interacting with this. I'm
not going to keep kowtowing. I'm not
going to keep being the bigger person
who comes and tries to soothe and smooth
because you're the boss. I'm not going
to do it.
So, that was the last day.
So, for anyone who's ever wanted to
know, you just got a random tea. That
was the last day.
There we go.
Okay, let's get that to tenebrous.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, tenebrous.
Yeah, I was not tenebrous about my
feelings moving forward after that.
Very clear. Very clear. Did y'all know
we covered that situation a while ago
when um she was on Club Shay Shay. Club
Shay Shay, she was given a platform to
come in and express herself, in which
she spoke on Issa Rae in that damn
interview. But after finding some middle
ground with Shannon, she then went home
and bashed that boy like crazy. Her fans
just kicking his man back in. Matter of
fact, let's take a quick walk down
memory lane so I can remind y'all of
that. Listen to this little bit. I felt
like Shannon was playing in my face.
And he eventually turned the corner, but
and then but then at the end of the
interview, like he just
Like I don't know, just kind of like
chilling.
Me and Shannon were flirting.
Ma'am, if you don't get all the way out
of here with that [ __ ] please.
Don't insult me.
Um
and
That was offensive.
That was highly offensive, and it makes
me wonder if you know
when people are flirting with you.
Um
So, when I left the interview, I just
was very like kind of not sure because
how it was going to play out, and I knew
that he had played himself in the
interview in a number of time in a
number of ways. And so, I knew that he
would um
they would probably edit some of it out.
So, that's how I felt.
Um
Have you seen his prior interviews?
He's very welcoming and bubbly.
He
the door is open.
Folks talk uninterrupted.
He allows them to be a safe space. The
producer told me I would be in a safe
space, and told me, you know, I'd be
able I would be supported.
So, that's what I expected.
>> [laughter]
>> He didn't behave with me like he had he
has not behaved with anybody else
like he did with me. So, that's why I
did the interview. Anyone she comes
in contact with, it's not a matter of
if, it's when she will fall out with
them. When this person going to rub her
the wrong way, and her response is going
to be very very flagrant, you know? And
she's entitled to whatever she has to do
to maintain her distance, keep herself
safe, and all that stuff as far as what
she got going on mentally. She's
entitled to that, but damn, every single
person?
Every single person? Hope everything
works out for her though, but I just
can't but help to notice this pattern,
you know? But hey though, y'all got to
let me know what you got to say in the
comment section below. I'm going to go
ahead and get up out of here though.
This is another update with Stace. Yo.